bizdays.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy: Business Search Engine and Business Directory -BizDays.com

**1\. What information BizDays.com collects from you.**

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

**Personal Information You Choose to Provide Registration:**  
You will provide us information about yourself, your firm or company, and your practices when you register your company info. You may also provide additional comments on how BizDays.com is servicing your needs and interests. If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. 

**Web Site Use Information:**  
Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. 

**2\. With whom your information may be shared.**  
BizDays.com will not sell, rent or barter your personal information other than to its business partners. However, we may report aggregate information to our advertisers. Such aggregate information will not individually identify any user.   
BizDays.com may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating BizDays.com's Terms of Use or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) BizDays.com's rights or property, other BizDays.com users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. BizDays.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.

**3\. How do we use the information that you provide to us?**  
BizDays.com uses personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable.

**4\. What are cookies?**  
As part of offering and providing personalized service, BizDays.com uses cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. A small amount of data is transferred to your computer's hard drive. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. All portions of the Site that prompt you to log in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies. No other company has access to cookies placed on your computer by BizDays.com. We may use cookies technology to reduce the time required for you to submit your requests and for BizDays.com to respond to such requests. 

**5\. How BizDays.com protects your personal information.**  
We make use of up to date and reasonable Internet security methods and technologies. We value our subscribers and work hard at keeping personal information from third parties. Password protection, use of encryption techniques and installation of firewalls are our most common forms of information protection. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, or that we transmit to you, or guarantee that it will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. What we can guarantee is that we will make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. 

**6\. What is BizDays.com's policy on allowing me to update, correct, or delete my personal information?**  
If you have a BizDays.com business listing you may modify, update or delete your listing and your confidential administrative contact information at any time by signing in. You will need your user name and password to access your listing.   
Should you decide to delete your BizDays.com business listing, it will no longer appear on our public site. However your original information may be retained within our database and on our backups. 

**7\. Consent**  
By using BizDays.com and by signing up for our services; you consent to the collection and use of the previously mentioned information by Jnetus, Inc. This privacy policy is subject to change. To stay up-to-date with our policies, please check this page frequently. We reserve the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time.

**8\. Feedback**  
Should you have a concern about BizDays.com's collection or use of your personal information, please contact us.
